oneacademy.eu 2016-11-18

# OneAcademy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The Company recognizes and supports the importance of protecting the privacy of information we may collect from you. To this end, we are committed to using our best efforts to respect your privacy. Below you will find our policies for how the Company handles information we collect from you from your visits to the OneAcademy website. The Company follows strictly all relevant Laws and Regulations.

**OneAcademy way of using information**

The profile information Users provide is protected by unique password and is accessible only by the User.

Users can change their Profile information at any time and can control how other Users and the Company communicates with them.

If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at info@oneacademy.eu

We receive and store information you enter on the OneAcademy website or give us in any other way. We use such information, including your name and e-mail address, for several purposes such as:

To process, fulfill and notify you of your product order status; and

To inform you about the latest information about our Company, updates in policies and procedures, promotions and changes in strategy.

From time to time we collect personal information from our Users. Where permitted by the provisions of applicable laws the Company may use and disclose such personal information about our Users. for the following purposes:

Administering Users benefits;

Developing and implementing policies, marketing plans and strategies;

Publishing personal information in company’s’ newsletters, promotional materials and company and intra-group communications;

Providing references; and

Complying with applicable laws and regulatory requirements and assisting with any governmental or police investigation; and

Other purposes directly relating to any of the above.

Additionally, User preferences and settings (time zone, language, privacy preferences, product preferences, etc.) may be collected to enhance the Service.

As is standard practice on many websites, the Company also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate User data, and browser type, from Users and other visitors to the site or application. This data is used to improve the Services, to analyze trends, to administer the Services, to track Users’ movements around the Service and to gather demographic information about our User base as a whole. The Company will not use the information collected to market directly to that person. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and special offers to Users. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

In addition, the Company and third parties may use pixel tags — tiny graphic images — to tell us what parts of our website Users have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches Users perform on our site, among other data. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in formats Users can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we’re only sending messages that are of interest to our Users. The Company stores the information we gather in a database stored on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. To the extent that third parties gather information, they store that information and are responsible for their use of the same. 

The Company may also use a User’s email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. The Company may send email communications which use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the OneAcademy website. When a User clicks one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. The Company tracks this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our Users communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

The Company may also collect information for market research purposes to gain a better understanding of our Users and thus provide more valuable service. The Company also collects information regarding User activities on our website, and on related websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to Users and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them.

**GEO-LOCATION-INFORMATION:**

While the OneAcademy website is in use, we may keep track of User’s device’s geographic location so that we can connect Users to other OneAcademy services based on their particular geographic location.

**USE OF COOKIES**

The Company may use cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same promotions, to customize newsletter and Web page content based on browser type and User profile information, to help track usage to help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there, to make usage of our website even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our User communications and to customize each visitor’s experience and provide greater convenience.

The Company does not link the information we store in cookies to any user-submitted personal information such as name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and age. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set — each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences — however, you must enable cookies from Company in order to use most functions on the site.   
The OneAcademy website deposits certain bits of information called "cookies" in a visitor's web browser software. Cookies are sent back only to the OneAcademy website that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site.

Cookies can tell us how and when pages in a OneAcademy website are visited and by how many people. We use cookies:

To allow you to use all password-protected services in a single session without having to re-enter your password; and

To track your site of origin.

**LINKS**

OneAcademy's website may contain links to third party websites. OneAcademy is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites or applications. When connecting to or linking to another site, a User should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on OneAcademy.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

As a resource to our visitors, we may provide links to other websites, which OneAcademy believe may be useful and meet our high standards of services.

Ads appearing on OneAcademy may be delivered to Users by OneAcademy or third party advertisers. These third parties may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer or mobile device each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer or mobile device, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers only the use of cookies by OneAcademy and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party advertisers.

**SECURITY**

We have implemented the necessary security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information you provide. When you become a User of OneAcademy or give us personal information, such as name, address, including any other information the Company may consider necessary for the accurate User identification, it is automatically saved on our secured server. Our secured server software encrypts the information you input before it is sent to us to protect your data against unauthorized access.

Please note that OneAcademy cannot guarantee the security of User account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. Users are urged to also take precautions to protect their personal data by changing passwords often using a specific combination of letters and numbers, and using a secure web browser. If you share a computer or mobile device with anyone, you should always log out of the Web site or application before leaving it to prevent access to your information from subsequent Users of that computer or device. For any additional information about the security measures OneAcademy uses on our website, please contact us at info@oneacademy.eu.

**SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION**

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, the Company will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by the Company, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Users or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and Users of the service. The Company reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of OneAcademy or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information, see the “Changes in Our Privacy Policy” section below. OneAcademy takes your privacy very seriously. OneAcademy does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. In order to provide the best possible level of service to our Users, your personal information may be shared with third party websites related to OneAcademy, who will safeguard it in accordance with OneAcademy’s Privacy Policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for OneAcademy to make certain personal information about you available to companies that OneAcademy has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for OneAcademy to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, deliver products to you, manage and enhance User data, provide User service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct User research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with OneAcademy’s policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive User service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the OneAcademy website or application.

**PRIVACY OF CHILDREN**

None of the OneAcadеmy sites or properties are directed to users under the age of 18.

**CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

From time to time OneAcademy may make changes to our Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make Users aware of what the changes are so Users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

**CONTACTING THE WEB SITE**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our Company, please contact us at: info@oneacademy.eu

**Third Parties**

We are not in the business of selling your personal information to third parties. Where permitted by the provisions of applicable law, the Company may though share such information from time to time with the following third parties:

Those employees, directors and managers of the Company and its local and foreign associated/affiliated companies who have a need to access your personal information in carrying out their responsibilities;

Any agent, contractor, supplier, vendor, or third party who provides administrative, advertising, printing, or other services to the Company or its affiliated companies, including but not limited to distribution centers, external auditors, trustees, insurance companies, actuaries;

Any government agency or other appropriate governmental, police, or regulatory authority or elsewhere in order to meet legal security and regulatory requirements.

**TRANSFER**

Any possible transfer of information will be administrated by the Company. By accepting the Terms and Conditions, by visiting this website and communicating electronically with us you hereby provide us with your explicit consent for such possible transfers.

The consent you have provided herein to the use of your personal information by the Company or its affiliates shall also extend to any person or corporation to which the Company may transfer its business, provided that such personal information is used for the same purposes. 

**ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You have the right to request and obtain from the Company the personal information available on file about you and request a correction of any data that is inaccurate, besides that information which can't be changed for security reasons. You may also request the Company to inform you of the type of personal information maintained by us. Requests for access to and correction of personal data or information about the Company policies and procedures regarding personal data should be addressed in writing at info@oneacademy.eu.

Questions, comments or suggestions about the Company in general, should also be e-mailed at info@oneacademy.eu

**ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS**

By accepting this Agreement you hereby agree, fully and with no objections, that the Company may provide all legal communications and notices to You electronically by posting them on our website or, at our election, by sending an email to the email address that you provided to us and/or to the email address that you currently are keeping in your profile section as an official email address of yours. You may, at any time, withdraw your consent to receive communications from the Company electronically by contacting our customer service by email provided at out website.

However, if You withdraw your consent to receive our communications electronically, You are at the same time discontinuing your use of your personal OneLife account, and thereby also all benefits connected to your personal rights as an Independent Marketing Associate.

_Effective as of 19.04.2016_
